-[insects chirping]
-[rumbling]
[dinosaurs bellowing]
[thudding]
[roars, screeches]
[kids panting]
[Ben] Ow!
[Bumpy squeals]
-Is everyone okay?
-Is everyone...? [chuckles]
Yaz, wait!
Wait! [grunts] Yasmina!
[both groaning]
-[Ben groans]
-[Bumpy squeals]
-[Yasmina] We're not okay!
-Yaz--
We're in the middle of a jungle
with a monster dinosaur out there,
and you...
You...
Destroyed our only way to get help
and lied about it!
I told you guys!
So, you did take Brooklynn's phone?
Why? What were you doing?
Probably trying to erase my video
of her taking those samples
from the Sinoceratops. [gasps]
And you knew about the Indominus rex
because you were snooping around
Dr. Wu's office when I ran into you.
-I knew it!
-I didn't mean to destroy the phone.
I fell on it when the zipline
came down and--
But you did steal it?
You had it that whole time
and didn't tell us?
Hold up. What were you doing
in Dr. Wu's office, Brooklynn?
I... It doesn't matter.
I didn't break our only way
to call for help and then lie about it!
This is not my fault! This is her fault!
-She--
-I'm here to spy!
For a company called Mantah Corp.
Mantah Corp?
They're a bioengineering company,
big rivals with Masrani.
They tried to make dinosaurs, too,
but Wu beat them to it.
You doomed us all for some lousy company?
Our ranch was in trouble,
so my folks had to borrow a lot of money
from some shady people.
We didn't know
they were fronting for Mantah Corp.
They said we'd lose everything
unless I spied for them.
Use the behind-the-scenes access I'd get
at camp to gather info from Wu's lab,
and DNA from dinos,
and whatever else they needed.
But then Brooklynn caught on,
and I got scared,
and then everything went wrong.
This is the last thing I wanted to happen.
Oh. [scoffs]
To be next to a broken van
on Killer Dinosaur Island?
Hey, me, too! What are the odds?
Yaz, I--
Was it all a lie, wanting to be friends?
Pretending you cared about...
You just needed someone
to hide what you were doing.
Tell me I'm wrong.
[sobs]
I'm such an idiot.
[Sammy] You are wrong!
I just didn't know how to say it,
how to explain to you.
Just because I spied
doesn't change who I am.
Don't touch me!
Go away, Sammy.
[gasps]
[whimpers, cries]
[Bumpy grunting]
Not now, Bumpy.
Look, I know the situation we're in
is suboptimal--
It's trash. Just say it's trash, Ben.
Yes, but despite
the obvious trashitude...
-[grunting]
-...we... we need to--
-Bumpy, what are you...
-[rumbling]
[roaring]
[all screaming]
[Ben] This is trash! This is trash!
-What the heck?
-[helicopter whirring]
[Ben grunts]
[gunfire]
Masrani's helicopter!
That's his call sign on the tail!
They're shooting at the Indominus!
[roaring]
-[squeals]
-[thuds]
-What was that?
-Yeah! Kick its butt, Masrani!
[whooping] We're saved!
Yeah, baby!
Ah! I told you, they've got it
totally under--
[explosion]
[Darius] With those pteranodons loose,
we're sitting ducks!
We've gotta take cover!
[gasps]
-[tablet beeps]
-The Kayak River!
The entrance is near here.
It goes underground, beneath the ridge.
If we follow it, it'll take us
right to the main park.
Then that's where we need to be.
Come on!
-[squealing]
-[both grunting]
Come on, Bumpy!
[screeching]
[Kenji screams]
Come on!
-[Kenji panting]
-[beeping continues]
-Hurry up!
-[grunts]
[panting]
[both grunting]
[Brooklynn] There it is!
-Bumpy! Come on, we need to go in!
-Come on, Bumpy!
[screeching]
-[both screaming]
-[screeching continues]
[Darius whimpers]
-[Ben grunts]
-[pteranodon screeches]
[all panting]
[automated voice] Jurassic World
River Adventures.
What?
Prepare yourselves for the wonder
of the underground river.
Two adventurers per kayak.
Life vests must be worn at all times.
Adults, please fasten your own life vests
before helping little adventurers.
Remain seated at all times.
Your journey begins now.
-Brooklynn and I call the CKK.
-CKK?
-Cool kids' kayak.
-[huffs]
-Ben and Bumpy can go in this one.
-I'll go with them.
[Sammy gasps]
-[Yasmina] Let's go, dude.
-Ah! [stammers] Okay.
[Bumpy grunts]
-[Yasmina groans, grunts]
-[Ben grunts]
Come on, Sammy, let's get out of here.
[automated voice] Ladies and gentlemen,
we'd like to thank you for your patience.
Darius, do you copy?
Kids, please answer.
[sighs] Still nothing.
Look! There's an ACU tablet and vehicle
on the move here.
That must be them!
They said they had a van,
but they're still not safe out there.
We've gotta get to them.
HQ, this is Roxie from Camp Cretaceous.
Do you copy?
[woman on radio] Who-- This frequency
is for emergency use only!
This is an emergency!
We've got kids in Sector Seven
outside the containment area, and--
Hey! Dave here.
Sounds like you got
your hands full over there.
Tell you what--
if you let us borrow a park vehicle,
we can just bring the kids in
ourselves, just--
No, we can't just let you
just take a vehicle!
Yours is not
the only emergency happening.
What? I don't know. I don't know.
They say they're from the camp.
[man on radio] We don't have time
for this. Clear the line!
Hello? Hello?
They hung up on me. They hung up on me!
If things are as bad as we think,
there's no way rescuing six kids
is gonna be their top priority.
What are we gonna do?
Jack a park vehicle,
go storming across the island?
-Stop!
-[man] Hey, you don't have authorization!
-Watch it!
-CKK has right of way.
Sorry, I don't make the rules.
Hey, the cave's getting bigger.
And brighter?
[both gasp]
[Bumpy groans]
Even with the glowy stuff,
it's really dark in here.
[muffled gasp]
I could have used my phone as a flashlight
if Sammy hadn't broken it.
Of course, if we had my phone,
we wouldn't be here at all.
Hey, will you stop harshing
the mellow of the CKK?
How many times are you gonna say "CKK"?
CKK? Why?
Would you like me to stop saying "CKK"?
CKK. CKK. CKK.
[sighs] You're acting like
this doesn't affect you, too.
We're here because of her.
Or maybe something else
would have happened
and we would still be stuck here.
Look, I-- I know you're mad at Sammy,
but getting mad
doesn't get us out of here.
It just makes more people mad, you know?
Put yourself in her shoes.
At this point, is there
anything you could say
that would make Sammy feel worse
than she already does?
Take it from someone
who has ample experience
in rubbing people the wrong way.
Just ask.
It's just that you talk so much
about your ranch and your family.
But your family sent you here
to break the law.
Don't, Darius.
You don't know anything about my family.
I know they put you in danger
when they sent you to spy on the park.
How can you still defend them?
Because they didn't send me.
They said "no" to Mantah Corp.
They said they'd rather lose everything
than use me like that.
I was the one who contacted
the Mantah Corp agent.
I agreed to come here.
My family...
they didn't even know what I was planning
until I was already on the ferry.
Smashing the phone was an accident,
but Brooklynn's right--
this is all my fault.
I still don't see why--
If your family was in trouble,
wouldn't you do anything in your power
to save them?
Ben, would you please put down
that overgrown turtle
and pick up your paddle?
I think Bumpy's seasick.
I think you need to paddle!
-[Bumpy groans]
-I think...
we both need to prepare for dino-vomit!
You guys, should the algae be moving?
[Kenji yelps]
[dinosaurs groan]
Don't panic, guys. They're herbivores!
Unbelievable!
Dr. Wu must have put the bioluminescent
gene into these Parasaurolophuses.
[groans]
What do you mean I insulted Bumpy?
You called her a turtle,
and now she's upset!
Ben, dinosaurs can't understand English!
Well, I'm glad she can't,
because there have been
several unkind things said.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry, Bumpy.
-[squeals]
-Oh, great! Now you made it worse.
[scoffs] Yep. This is the kayak I picked.
[squealing]
[groaning]
-[Darius gasps]
-[Sammy] Whoa! [whimpers]
[both yelp]
Yeah. Cool.
-[Darius gasps]
-[groans]
-[Ben whimpers]
-[Bumpy squeals]
[all gasping, grunting]
[squealing]
-[bellowing]
-[grunts]
-Whoa!
-[whimpering]
Hmm?
[bellows]
-Uh, cool kids to nerds, where are you?
-[Darius] Over here!
I think something scared
the Parasaurolophuses.
Darius, if we stopped paddling,
why are we still moving forward?
[Darius gasps]
[yelps] Paddle! There's a current
pulling us into a different tunnel.
[grunting]
[Darius] No! Guys!
[all screaming]
[screaming continues]
[panting]
-[boats thud]
-[Kenji grunts]
-[Bumpy groaning]
-[sighs] We're okay. We're okay.
-[Sammy laughs]
-[Bumpy squeals]
What? [gasps]
Why did you gasp?
It didn't sound like a good gasp!
'Cause I know exactly where we are, guys.
We're in the Jurassic World Lagoon.
And so is the Mosasaurus.
[both gasp]
I assume the Mosasaurus
is some kind of giant fish dinosaur
that's gonna try and eat us.
-[yelps]
-[low growling]
[whimpers]
It's circling, testing us.
It's acting like a shark.
We're intruders in its domain,
so it's investigating us.
Before it gets confident,
decides to... to...
[snarling]
-[whimpers]
-[squeals]
-This is bad.
-We have to get out now!
There's a ladder by the spectator stands.
-[Kenji] How are we gonna--
-[whimpers] Y'all?
[low growling]
-Paddle! Go, go, go!
-[Sammy whimpering]
This is not how Kenji wanted to go out!
This isn't on my to-do list either!
-[Brooklynn] Come on!
-[Darius] Hey!
[Roxie] The kids must have gone in.
The river leads to the main park, right?
There's no way that'll pick up
their signal under all that rock.
[Dave] I see 'em!
They're not on the river anymore.
They're in Aquatic Area One.
[tires screech]
[pants, grunts]
Keep paddling!
Almost there!
[squealing]
[Yasmina gasps]
[both panting]
Don't look back!
[grunting]
[Sammy screams]
-[whimpers]
-[Darius] No!
[both panting]
No.
[Ben panting]
[Yasmina panting]
Yaz, what are you doing?
Whatever you do, don't stop paddling!
[grunting]
-Yasmina--
-Just keep paddling!
[Sammy whimpering]
-[Bumpy groans]
-[Ben grunts]
Come on, faster!
Don't look back, Sammy!
Just keep paddling!
I'm trying!
What's Yaz doing?
[gasps, exhales]
Hey! Hey! Over here!
Hey!
-[muffled thudding]
-[growls]
-[Yasmina] Over here!
-[gasps]
Here! Here!
Yes! Here!
She's distracting it, buying us time.
Keep going!
[laughs]
Yes!
-Yes! She did it!
-Yes, Jaz!
I did not think this through.
We gotta do something!
[whirring]
-[gasps]
-Grab the chain!
[grunts]
-[Brooklynn] Go, go, go!
-[Ben] Yasmina!
[grunts]
No! [whimpers]
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Come on, Yaz!
[grunts]
-Oh, no...
-She's not gonna make it.
[growling]
[grunts, yells]
[yelling continues]
-[grunts]
-Yasmina!
-[whimpers]
-[Yasmina groans]
I'm okay.
[grunts, pants]
I think.
Uh, also, where'd everyone go?
[beeping fades]
Rox, it's gone. The kids' signal is gone!
It's probably just a glitch, right?
Reboot the system.
Come on! Come on!
Give me something! Give me something!
-[tires screech]
-[dinosaurs screech]
[tablet beeps]
It's working.
Their signal just stopped.
[automated voice] Wednesdays are
k-k-kids-eat-free days
h-here at Jurassic World!
[Yasmina pants]
[grunts, pants]
Thank you for saving us,
for saving me.
That was amazing. You're amazing.
Stop.
[grunts]
[sighs]
We may need each other to stay alive,
but don't for a second think
that makes us friends again.
Because we're not and we will never be.
[grunting]
[Brooklynn] You okay?
Naw.
Not really.
Yeah.
Dumb question.
I don't know her that well,
but I think if you give Yaz some space,
she'll come around.
Maybe?
I don't know, I'm gonna be honest--
IRL friendships
aren't really my thing, but, uh...
sounds right, yeah?
Why are you being so nice to me?
Because Kenji is right.
Ugh, that feels so wrong to say.
Never, ever repeat that. Ugh. Gross.
[sighs]
Listen, I've done
my share of selfish things.
I only knew what you were up to because
I was also sneaking in places I shouldn't.
You were at least doing it for family.
I was doing it to impress
a bunch of angry internet randos.
Plus, when we get out of here,
you're gonna give me the exclusive
on all the juicy details
of you spying for Mantah Corp.
"Brooklynn Unboxes a Conspiracy."
Pow, pow!
Try to tell me my videos are lame
after that, angry internet randos!
-[giggles]
-So...
deal?
Deal.
So, not to be a total downer,
but Operation Find People
to Help Us is, heh...
clearly a bust.
My dad talked about coming here for years.
And here we are.
[Kenji] Yep.
Welcome to Jurassic World.
[screeching in distance]
[alarm blaring]
[Bumpy groans]
[blaring continues]